(Penny:)Okay, does everyone
remember the rules?
(Penny:)If he's shirtless, one sip.
(Penny:)Posing with a pet, two sips.
(Penny:)Pet and shirtless,
chug like it's your job.
And pull!
(Raj:)I have that
same underwear!
Chug!
(phone chimes)
Mm, Amy,
you're getting a text.
(Amy:)Oh, um, give me that.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
“I had a great time last night”"
No, no, st-stop reading that.
(Howard:)Who's Dave?
I...
(Penny:)You went on a date last night?
(Penny:)Are you seeing someone?
No, it-it's not like that.
(phone chimes)
“And I'd love to take you
out again”?
Amy!
What?
(All:)Can't believe it.
Oh, my God.
(Amy:)Okay, it's like that.
(Leonard:)Thank you for coming back.
(Man:)Yeah, well, normally I wouldn't,
(Man:)but my daughter's having
a sleepover, and there's only
(Man:)so much screaming and Katy Perry
a man can take.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, if you could just
give us our money back,